麦克斯 瞧瞧这午夜骑行活动
Max, look at all these customers
给我们带来多少顾客
from Brooklyn midnight ride,
我闻到了成功的味道
I smell of diner success!
真的吗 我只闻到胯下烤焦的味道呢
Really? 'Cause I smell baked crotch.
蛋蛋也能放屁吗
Can balls fart?
我感觉好像闻到了蛋屁味
Because I feel like I'm smelling that too.
奥列格怎么还没上我的菜
Where is Oleg with my orders?
我的客人再没拿到吃的 他们会...
If my tables don't get food soon, they're gonna--
天啊 他们果然举手示意了
Oh, my God, they're raising their arms.
我们也可以确定这次骑行
Ugh! Well, we know it wasn't a charity ride
不是为除臭剂募捐善款了
to raise money for deodorant.
奥列格 我的汉堡好了吗
Oleg, where are my burgers?
我现在有点大麻
I'm a little in the weeds right now.
你是说你抽了点大麻吧
You mean you smoked a little weed right now?
是药用大麻
It's medicinal.
压制我"长勃不倒"的毛病
Helps with my chronic erection.
有非感恩而死乐队成员
Can someone who's not in the Grateful Dead
能告诉我怎么才能弄到食物吗
tell me how we're gonna get food?
跟我来
Follow me.
你搞定盘子 汉堡面包 卷心菜沙拉
You do plates, buns, coleslaw.
我来搞汉堡 薯条
I'll do burgers, fries,
以及"搞"任何没未来的男人
and any guy who has no future.
你能想象如果我们生在贝壳里
Can you imagine if we were born inside shells,
然后有更强大的动物破开壳 吞我们下肚吗
and then even bigger animals cracked us open to eat?
薯条要放上盘子了
Fries on the plates!
没有人把这句金玉良言记下吗
Is anybody writing this gold down?
好了 奥列格 我要加入
All right, Oleg. I want in.
你抽的在...
Where's the--
或是...
or the--
又或是...
天啊 老子成聋子了
Oh, my God, am I deaf?
慢着 我把它放哪里了
Wait, where is it?
我记得放在某处了
I put it somewhere.
哇 有薯条吃[抽完大麻容易肚子饿]
Ooh, a french fry.
我不知道你们自行车练到什么程度了
I don't know where you guys are in your bike training.
是要来点兴奋剂 还是上甜点呢
Are we doping or desserting?
我都能帮你们搞到哦
I can help you either way.
我们想吃甜点
We're thinking about dessert.
很好 那来个麦克斯自制小蛋糕如何
Cool, how about a Max's homemade cupcake?
不要
Eh, I don't think so.
-樱桃派怎么样 -还不错
- How's that cherry pie? - Nice.
住在派里的那家老鼠 刚续租了
The family of mice that lives in it just renewed their lease.
还是来个麦克斯自制小蛋糕吧
So, a Max's homemade cupcake?
你干嘛一直提"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
You keep saying "Max's homemade cupcakes"
好像多出名一样
like it's a thing.
我从来没听说过这玩意
I've never heard of it.
我也是 我们可是很懂行的呢
I haven't either. And we know a lot.
但你出门还是系了这个二逼头巾
And yet you put that headband on this morning.
-那个麦克斯是谁啊 -对啊 是谁啊
- So who's Max? - Yeah, who's Max?
谁是麦克斯啊
Who's Max?
她是兰斯·阿姆斯特朗的左蛋蛋
She's Lance Armstrong's left nut.
-看你妹啊 -不看不看
- What? - Nothing.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
你知道我不喜欢说人八卦
You know I'm not one to gossip,
但就在30秒之前
but just about 30 seconds ago,
我亲眼看见麦克斯耍脾气
I saw Max drop some major attitude
葬送了一个争取小蛋糕潜在客户的机会
and blow a chance with a possible cupcake customer.
你的八卦就是这个吗
That's your gossip?
谁不知道麦克斯脾气大啊
That Max has an attitude?
你接下来还要跟我八卦什么
What are you gonna tell me next,
艾尔顿·约翰是同性恋吗
that Elton John is gay?
总而言之 我就说说而已
Anyways, I'm just saying about Max,
那贱人不该气焰这么嚣张
bitch needs to take it down a notch.
那你这个贱人 应该少管闲事
Bitch needs to mind his own business.
麦克斯 你今晚是不是吹了一个潜在的客户
Max, did you blow a possible cupcake customer tonight?
我可是公私分明 干活时候从不"吹"
You know I don't mix business with pleasure.
我们必须不断地推销小蛋糕
We have to keep pushing our cupcakes.
每个餐桌 每次点餐
Every table, every time,
-都要强推"麦克斯自制小蛋糕" -我有啊
- "Max's homemade cupcakes." - I did.
刚才我说我名字的次数
I said my name to that table more times
比我妈这辈子叫我的次数还多
than my mother said it my entire life.
你不能光说名字
But you can't just say the name.
你得用心去推销
You have to really sell it.
你真应该向我学着点
You should see me out there.
"希望您肚子还有空位
"hope you saved room for
吃我们美味的麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
one of our delicious "Max's homemade cupcakes.
-"湿润 味美 带汁液" -别说了
- "they're moist, delicious, creamy--" - Stop.
没想到我会说这个
I can't believe I'm saying this,
但老娘又不是妓女
but I am not a whore.
你就是个小蛋糕妓女
Oh, you're a cupcake whore,
而现在我是你的皮条客 所以...
and right now I'm your pimp, so...
-你今晚卖了多少 -两个
- how many did you sell tonight? - Two.
别打我 皮条老爹
Don't hit me, daddy!
好吧 那你今晚又卖了多少
Okay, how many did you sell tonight?
我可是卖了
I sold...
两个哟
Two.
好吧 我们是一代烂妓
Okay, we're bad whores.
不 我们只是累了的妓
No, we are tired whores.
急什么 又不是世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
我们不过是因为"手腕累了"
We're just letting a few El-Caminos drive by
才放过几个开老爷车的过路客
because our wrists are sore.
我就爱你这样
I love you for that.
你看待事物总是有独到见解
You just put everything into perspective.
于是我跟卡洛琳说 这样对生意不好
So I says to Caroline, "it's so bad for business."
她们现在正在厨房大吵特吵呢
And right now they're in the kitchen having huge fight.
我真的很担心...
I really worried that--
八卦小天后说你们的生意有"大麻烦"
Lady chatterbox says your business is in big trouble.
拜托 对小不点来说什么不"大"呀
Please, everything seems big to Han.
可以走了吗 苏菲
Ready to go, Sophie?
姑娘们 听说你们的生意失败
And girls, sorry to hear your business broke up
还撕破脸了啊
and you aren't speaking.
我们吓到他了
We scared him.
这小鼠辈要躲回灶台下了
Now he's gonna run under the stove.
我会打几个电话帮帮你们
I'm gonna make some calls to help you.
给你们接几个大派对单子
Get you some big party jobs.
你人真好 苏菲
That's so nice of you, Sophie.
我们感激不尽
We really appreciate it.
你们俩姑娘可以挣大钱哦
You girls can make some big money.
你们也知道 高大节要来了
As you know, Duza day is coming up.
不 我不知道
Um, no, I do not know.
什么是高大节呀
What the hell is Duza day?
高大节是波兰的重大节日
Oh, Duza day is huge holiday in Polish community.
当波兰姑娘长到1米82时
When a polish girl reaches six feet,
得给她办个派对
You give her big party.
我是在七岁的时候办的
I had mine when I was seven.
是"私事"在笑
Is this private giggling
还是我也可以加入啊
or can anyone join?
-你在看什么啊 -我最爱的节目
- What are you watching? - My favorite show.
"阿比与布莱缇"的节目吗
Abby & Brittany, the show about those
连体婴姐妹 一个身子两个头
cute conjoined twins with two heads, one torso?
看过了
Already watched it.
她们为了一条项链吵架了
They fought about a necklace.
我现在是看决战小蛋糕之巅
Now I'm watching Cupcake Wars.
如果我们队伍赢了比赛
If our team wins Cupcake Wars,
我们将用这一万元奖金
we're gonna use the $10,000 prize
来开一家属于我们的小店
to finally open up our own storefront.
等等 一万元 这是什么节目
Wait, $10,000? What kind of show is this?
我还以为有了谷歌之后
I thought Google eliminated the need
就不会有人随口问蠢问题了
to ask questions out loud, but fine.
这是美食频道的节目
It's a show on Food Network
那为什么我们不参加
And why are we not on it?
看那个傻蛋
Look at that dumb-dumb!
她裱花袋都掉地上了
She just dropped the pastry bag.
那器官叫"双手"
Hey, they're called hands,
学学怎么用它们吧 傻蛋
learn how to use them, dumb-dumb!
这就是为什么我们不去参加
And that is why we're not on it.
不是每个人都跟你一样爱批判
Not everyone's as judgmental as you.
哪个人不跟我一样爱批判啊
Oh, everyone's as judgmental as me.
我也不想有无礼的臭三八
And I don't need some snarky bitch
指着她的电视说
pointing at us on her TV going,
"快看电视上那金发傻蛋
"oh, look at that blonde dumb-dumb
跟她那个性感努力在忙活的朋友"
and her hot friend trying to do something."
麦克斯 为什么你从不让自己有梦想呢
Max, why don't you ever let yourself dream?
因为在我梦中
Because in my dreams,
我眼珠总是被蜘蛛吃了
spiders are always eating my eyes.
这没准是我们需要的大机遇
This might be the big push we need.
我们可以去决战小蛋糕之巅
We can go on Cupcake Wars,
也可以继续当小蛋糕之妓
or we can keep being cupcake whores.
你考虑一下吧
Think about it.
我们不用路上逢人就求"卖"
We wouldn't have to go car-to-car anymore,
而是可以开家正经的妓院
we could actually open a brothel.
等等 如果可以选择去妓院
Wait, if brothel's on the table,
那我们还想着这个破蛋糕生意干嘛
why don't we just forget about this cupcake thing?
做那份工 我就可以不穿裤子上班了
'cause that's a job I can do without pants.
说真的 好歹也去美食频道试着报名看看吧
Seriously. Let's at least go to the Food Network and apply.
不是这样的
That's not how it works.
你得在网上先填报名表
You fill out an application online,
并上传一个两分钟的自我介绍短片
submit a two-minute home video,
然后节目组会在八到十天后通知你
and then wait eight to ten days for a response.
让我逮到你有过这个梦吧
Huh, caught you dreaming.
行 我是曾经想过那么一秒钟
All right, so maybe I thought about it for, like, a second,
在我们刚刚组队的那会
when we first became a team.
但我想起人生就是个死胡同
But then I remembered the world's a dead-end
好事永远也不会降临
and nothing good happens ever to anyone.
那抽屉里有把枪
There's a gun in that drawer.
不如现在就饮弹自尽吧
Do you want to just kill ourselves?
麦克斯
Oh, Max.
你终于承认我们是一个团队了
You finally called us a team.
我们绝对要上那节目
We are so going on that show.
说真的 我真不知道连体婴姐妹忍受的
Seriously, I don't know how Abby and Brittany do it,
光是你跟我坐这么近
because I'm uncomfortable with you
我就浑身不舒服了
even sitting this close to me.
如果我们要给名为"世界最不舒服T恤"的
Well, if we're making an audition tape to be on a reality show called,
真人秀拍试镜带
"The world's most uncomfortable T-shirt,"
那我们已经赢了
We have already won.
我是可以买更贵的衣服
Yes, I could have gotten us
例如去AA美国服饰店买[平价服饰]
a more expensive shirt at American Apparel,
但那样只会让我们看起来像装穷
but then we would just look like people pretending to be poor.
估计还像卖淫的13岁屁孩
And 13, and probably in the sex trade.
我没想到你居然省到用直发器
I cannot believe you used your flat iron
来把图案给烫上
to put these letters on.
我也不敢相信你会用过这来压三明治啊
Well, I can't believe you once used it to make a panini,
但你还不是做了
but--that's what happens now.
剪刀呢
Where's the scissors?
我要给这衣服加点风采
I gotta give this thing some flave.
麦克斯 你在干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
圆领衫是给乡巴佬跟摩门教徒穿的
Crew necks are for squares and Mormons.
真可爱 我该学你吗
Oh, cute! Should we do mine?
我不知道
I don't know.
内里无"车" 何须打开"车库"
If you have no car, why open the garage?
我觉得我们就站这里拍
So, I thought we'd shoot it over here
在我们有爱 凄凉 又穷酸的厨房里
in our adorable, scrappy, low-income kitchen.
你干嘛这么说话
Why are you talking like that?
这就是我们的品牌风格啊
Because that's our brand.
我看了无数集决战小蛋糕之巅
I've watched a ton of Cupcake Wars,
打出自我品牌是很重要的一环
and it's a lot about branding.
那我们是什么
And what are we?
会做小蛋糕的女孩加
The girl who knows how to make cupcakes
不会做的女孩组合吗
and the girl who doesn't?
麦克斯 我才不担心这个
Max, I'm not worried about that.
你会告诉我怎么做 就跟往常一样
You'll just tell me what to do, like you always do,
然后我们就扮演两个凄凉穷苦的女孩
and we'll be the two scrappy girls with so little
哪有观众会不心疼我们啊
you can't help but love them.
我已经开始讨厌这俩妞了
I hate them already.
奥列格来了
Okay, that's Oleg.
你有告诉他是来拍试镜带
You did tell him he's filming us for an audition
而不是来拍黄片的吧
and not making a porno, right?
有的 我说得非常清楚
Yeah, I made it very clear.
你们怎么还穿着上衣啊
Why are your tops still on?
塑料布怎么还不铺好啊
And why isn't the plastic down?
油会溅的到处都是呢
You're gonna get oil everywhere.
奥列格 麦克斯说过了
Oleg, Max told you
我们不是要拍"那种"电影
we're not gonna make that kind of movie.
但每个跟我合作过"后庭新娘"电影的
I know, but so did every girl that I worked with
女孩也都这么说啊
on "Backdoor Brides".
然后拍续集时又说了一遍
And then again on "Backdoor Brides II."
但开拍五分钟过后 就成了新娘"来"了
But five minutes later, it was "here comes the bride."
太好了
Oh, good.
你们上衣还在
You still have your tops on.
她们不用拍女女黄片赚钱了
Yeah, they don't have to make Girl-on-girl porn film for money.
我帮你们接到了高大节的单
I got you big Duza day party.
三百个小蛋糕
300 cupcakes!
天啊 能赚一千两百块呢
Oh, my God! That's $1,200.
不 不给钱
No, it's for free.
这次是让你们打通关系
You do it for connections,
好让你们在波兰饺子自助上提供甜点
and for the hot and cold pierogi buffet.
苏菲 我不确定
Oh, Sophie, I don't know
是否该接你这免费的活
if we should be taking free work right now.
我们想上电视 如果雀屏中选
We're doing this TV thing, and if we get it,
我们的时间就不好拿捏
we don't know what our schedule will be.
不知道你们是警花拍档
Oh, I didn't know I was talking
是我有眼不识泰山
to Cagney and Lacey.
好吧 随你们
Yeah, well, suit yourself.
对不起 苏菲
We're sorry, Sophie.
你完全有权气我们
You have every right to be mad.
吃个小蛋糕心情会好点吗
Would a cupcake help?
当然会
Always.
我发短信叫另一个女孩别来了
Well, I just texted the third girl not to come,
咱们速战速决吧
So let's get this over with.
好兴奋哦 我们可以的
This is so exciting. We're gonna be great.
-我们一定行 姐妹 -停
- We got this, girl. - Okay, stop.
我们绝不许说
On every reality show,
每个真人秀都会有人说的烂句
people say lame things that we can never say.
我们不许击拳 击掌
No fist bumping. No high fives.
不许叫我"使出全力" "发功"
You can't tell me to "bring it," "shut it down,"
或说要将小蛋糕生意名扬天下
or "put our cupcake business on the map."
也不许说 "加油妹子" "使出十成功力啊"
You can't tell me to "go, girl""or "bring my 'A' game,"
我们也没有"一定行" 懂吗
And we don't "got this". Cool?
懂
Cool.
-懂 但我们一定行 对吧 -那当然
- But we do got this, right? - Yeah, we got this.
好的 姑娘们 好戏上场
Okay, here we go, girls.
翘起你的屁屁 抱歉 职业病
Arch your backs. Sorry, force of habit.
开始
Action.
大家好吗 我是麦克斯
Hey, what's up? I'm Max,
她是我的搭档卡洛琳
And this is my partner, Caroline.
我们是"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
And we're Max's homemade cupcakes.
也就是"卖客湿"自制小蛋糕 来"卖"的
And by homemade, I mean, "hoe-made".
说得好 姑娘们
You go, girl!
-我们目前只是个网店 -我们有网站
- We are an online bakery... - Well, we have a website.
但大本营就在此 布鲁克林的威廉斯堡
And we're based right here in Williamsburg, Brooklyn.
小蛋糕的奇迹就是在此地创造的
And this is where the magic happens.
这里是厨房兼客厅兼我的卧房
This is our kitchen/ living room/ my bedroom --
还"奸"我的手腕 我总是烘培整晚
Slash my wrists, 'cause I'm trying to bake all night
而她只会呼呼大睡
while she's sleeping over there.
而这是我们的紫色烤箱
And here is our purple stove.
我们虽然人穷
Just because you're poor,
但风格品味绝不穷
that doesn't mean you can't have style.
还有只不请自来的抢镜马
Or a horse that just came in unannounced.
他是栗宝
Oh, this is Chestnut.
我们的试吃员
He's our test audience.
我们没有喂他巧克力哦
But we don't feed him chocolate.
因为马吃了会死
'Cause that would kill him.
她们还有匹马
They have a horse!
请您选我们 我们很努力也爱您的节目
So pick us because we're hard workers, we love the show,
而且我们是一对自食其力的姐妹花哦
and we're females getting their own, on their own.
停 拍得太棒了
And cut! That was so great.
还有栗宝突然就蹦了进来
Chestnut walking in out of nowhere,
真是老天的安排啊
we could not have planned that.
不 是我安排的
Oh, but I did.
这是我们的吸睛绝招 谁能赢啊
That's our gimmick. Try to beat that.
两女一马
Two girls with a horse.
这怎么就不是黄片啊
And how is this not a porn film?
我们知 我们行
We knew it, we got it
我早知 我已见
I knew it, I saw it!
你嘲笑上节目的傻蛋们时
Is this how you imagined it when you were laughing
有想到过此情此景吗
at all the dumb-dumbs on Cupcake Wars?
我真不敢相信我有来试镜
I cannot believe I am auditioning
这节目的一天
to be on Cupcake Wars.
我上了我爱看的节目
I am on the show I watch!
人生真是太美好了
Life is totally awesome.
早安 我是决战小蛋糕之巅的
Good morning. I'm the Cupcake Wars
你超牛逼 你的节目超牛逼
You are awesome. Your show's awesome.
我想拿个纪念马克杯的话 该找谁要呢
Who would I talk to about getting a mug to take home?
这里不是礼品店
Not a gift shop.
洁尼丝 我是卡洛琳 她是麦克斯
Janis, hi, I'm Caroline, and this is my partner, Max.
很喜欢你们的影带 很有个性
Loved your tape. Great characters.
-是吗 -是的
- We are? - We are.
我们将从队伍自我介绍开始
Look, we're about to start with the team intros.
另一队先 然后换你们
The other team is up first and then you.
记得是B.Y.O.B
And remember to B.Y.O.B.
早知道允许自己带酒来
Oh, if I had known I was allowed to bring a bottle in,
我就不把它们倒掉了
I wouldn't have chugged it in the bathroom.
麦克斯 她不是这意思
Max, that's not what she meant.
美食频道是很老少皆宜的
The Food Network is very PG.
洁妮丝 B.Y.O.B是指...
Janis, B.Y.O.B.?
"打出自己的品牌特色"
"Bring your own brand."
就像你们录制的影片一样
Just like you did on your home tape.
你是犀利巨乳姐 你是装模作样妞
You're edgy with big boobs. You're the "try hard."
抱歉 您说我是...
I'm sorry, I'm the what?
那是你们的招牌
That's your brand.
一个干活 一个废话
The muscle and the hustle.
"胸器逼人"与"傻逼人"
The double-D's and the ditz.
我上过沃顿商学院 我才不是傻逼
I went to Wharton. I'm not a ditz.
你也不是"胸器逼人啊"
Well you ain't the double-D's.
她居然这么直接地夸赞我的"胸器"
Can you believe she openly commented on m'goods?
好的 第一组请上场
All right, we're ready for team one.
请上前
Step up.
你们有三十秒
You have 30 seconds.
好的 围裙挺可爱 但品牌特色呢
Okay, cute aprons. But what's their brand?
倒数5 4 3 2...
In five, four, three, two...
大家好 我是法丽莎 我是布兰琪
Hi, I'm Felicia. And I'm Blanche,
我们是来自新月城的代表
and we're representing the crescent city.
也就是新奥尔良哟 各位
We're talking about New Orleans, y'all!
口音挺可爱 但没人能比我们凄凉悲惨
Cute accents, but no one has a scrappier story than us.
回想起2005年 卡特里娜飓风来袭
Back in 2005, when hurricane Katrina hit...
什么
Say what?
当时堤防溃堤
And the levee broke
我们那一带全淹没了
and flooded our whole neighborhood.
什么
Say what?
社区陷入愁云惨雾 我们心想
Our community was devastated, and we thought,
"卡特里娜淹掉了我们的家园"
"hell yes, Katrina hit us hard."
"但它淹不掉我们的魂与希望"
"But hell no! We're not giving up."
我们得想个办法 帮大家坚持下去
We needed to find a way to keep on keepin' on.
卡特里娜 她们是打飓风牌吗
Katrina? Their brand is Katrina?
我的"胸器"镇不住这招啊
Even m'goods can't upstage that.
我们想赢得这比赛
We want to win Cupcake Wars
这样我们才能有足够的资金
so we can finally open a storefront
在社区开个小店
in our little neighborhood.
让我们的生意正式上轨道
Make our business official.
这也是我们想回馈社区办法
Yeah, and find a way to put money back into our community.
这就是我们的理念
That's what we're all about at...
敦亲睦邻小蛋糕
Neighbor cakes!
加油
Boom!
很好 非常好
Great, great.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕 到你们了
Max's Homemade Cupcakes, you're up.
我们为啥会用我名字来当店名
Why did we name the company after me?
"敦亲睦邻小蛋糕"对比
"Neighbor Cakes" versus
"麦克斯自恋小蛋糕"
"Max's narcissistic cupcakes"?
没事的 理智线别断
We're fine. Don't freak out.
跟着我们的计划走 照搬家里那套
Just do our thing, like we did at home.
不必恐慌
No need to panic.
倒数5 4 3 2...
In five, four, three, two...
大家好啊
Yo, what's up?
我是"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"的麦克斯
I'm Max, of Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
是"卖客湿"自制小蛋糕 懂吗
They're "Hoe-made." Ha! Get it?
因为她是来卖的
'cause she's a hoe!
她有大"胸器"
She's got the boobs,
我有好头脑 对吧 麦克斯
And I've got the brains, right, Max?
算是吧
Uh, kind of.
我们的小蛋糕都是在家里烘焙的 环境...
We bake at home in our apartment, which is--
简直就像飓风扫过 真的很惨哦
Is a disaster area. Really, it's a mess.
而且我们还付不起房租
And we don't have our rent.
付不起房租 贵到我想哭
The rent is high, not gonna lie.
可怜无人助 也无男人顾
we hung out to dry, neither has a guy
咋样啊 决战小蛋糕之巅 对吧 麦克斯
Yo, what up, Cupcake Wars? Right, Max?
我不知道现在是怎样
I don't even know what's happening.
我们开始烘焙是因为我家破产
We bake because I lost all my money
而且她妈是酒鬼
and her mom drinks.
对了 我是卡洛琳 就此结束
Oh, I'm Caroline... and, cut.
好吧 行
Okay. Well, okay.
我刚才即兴唱了段饶舌吗
Did I just freestyle rap?
是的
Yes.
你还在家园被飓风淹没的女人面前
And you also called our apartment a disaster
说我们的家像是被飓风扫过一般
in front of two ladies whose apartments washed away.
你们俩没事吧
Hi. Everything okay over here?
傻逼人与胸器逼人一切正常
Yep. Ditz and double-D's, on track.
-介绍自己的品牌特色 -很好
- B.Y.O.B. - Great.
都来到台前 我将公布今天的神秘材料
Can we all gather to reveal the secret ingredients?
-会是什么材料啊 -都有可能啊
- What's it gonna be? - It could be anything.
在圣帕特里克节主题集中 有支队伍做了
I once saw a St. Patrick's day theme where a team made
啤酒幸运符小蛋糕
a beer and lucky charms cupcake.
那方面你很专长 希望是那个主题
That's right up your alley. I hope it's that.
今日的主题是
Today's theme is...
灵魂食物[黑人食物]
Soul food.
我们一定行的 姐妹
Ooh, we got this, sister!
胜券在握了 爽哟
Sister, this is gotten. Whoo-hoo!
材料包含有
Some of the ingredients include
秋葵 糖蜜 芥蓝 地瓜
okra, molasses, collard greens, sweet potato,
酪乳 鸡 猪蹄膀
buttermilk, chicken, and ham hock.
猪蹄膀
Ham hock?
怎么听起来像魔戒哈比人的名字
Isn't that a character in The Hobbit?
倒数3 2
In three, two...
比赛开始 女孩们
Here we go, girl!
姐妹 我们死定了
Sister, we are screwed.
我们可以做我们的地瓜泥小蛋糕
We can do our sweet potato mash cupcake.
再撒上糖蜜花生碎
Ooh, with peanut molasses drizzle.
秋葵小蛋糕 秋葵小蛋糕
Gumbo cupcake! Gumbo cupcake!
我们该怎么做
What are we gonna do?
不知道
I don't know.
-你在看什么 -摄影机啊
- What are you looking at? - The camera.
新奥尔良 新奥尔良
New Orleans, New Orleans
我们一定行 秋葵小蛋糕
we got this, gumbo cupcakes
卡洛琳 祝你好运
Good luck, Caroline.
不许走 麦克斯 跑什么跑啊
Stop it, Max. What's wrong with you?
最惨的事发生了 我们是这集里的傻蛋
It's happening. We're the dumb-dumbs!
我们才不是这集的傻蛋
We are not the dumb-dumbs.
我是沃顿商学院毕业的
I went to Wharton.
我们就选出三个材料吧
All we have to do is pick three ingredients.
我们准备好要放进烤箱了
And we're ready to pop them in the oven!
她们怎么这么快就能送入烤箱啦
How can they already be going in the oven?
-这让我有个主意 -什么
- Oh, that gives me an idea! - What?
把我放进烤箱吧
Put me in the oven!
没事的 先开始 边做边想吧
Okay, okay. We just have to start.
灵感会来的
It'll come to us.
统统带过去
Bring it all.
这集主题居然是灵魂食物
Just my luck to get soul food
我这没灵魂的人真是超"幸运"啊
when I don't even have a soul.
新奥尔良 新奥尔良
New Orleans, New Orleans
我们一定行 秋葵小蛋糕
we got this, gumbo cupcakes
这洗不了我的脑的
That is not catching on!
你有什么想法呢 麦克斯
So, what are you thinking, Max?
新奥尔良 新奥尔良
New Orleans, New Orleans
我错了 真被洗脑了
I was wrong, it is catching on.
别想那个了
Stop thinking that.
快想要用什么材料
Start thinking about the ingredients,
我一边先准备烘焙
while I do the baking.
我看你做过无数次了
I've seen you do it a million times.
用牛奶就行了 对吧
We just need milk, right, Max?
我们一定行 秋葵小蛋糕
We got this. Gumbo cupcakes
牛奶先拿来
Here's the milk.
我要先倒牛奶进搅拌器
So, I'll just pour this milk into this mixer.
看起来像我在烘焙 对吧 麦克斯
It looks like I'm baking, right, Max?
你眼睛看着呀
Whoa! Watch what you're doing!
淹水啦 发大水啦
It's flooding! It's flooding!
这就喊淹水呢
Oh, great, you said "flooding."
等等喊啥 防灾部跟飓风避难所了吗
What's next, "FEMA?" "Superdome?"
这真是场灾难
This is a disaster.
我们是节目史上最烂的一组了
We are the worst team ever.
我们才不是呢 你在干嘛
We are not. What are you doing?
偷点虾子带回家啊
Putting shrimp in my pocket to take home.
赢不了也不能空手而回吧
We gotta get something out of this.
赶紧开始试味道
Just start tasting this stuff
才好决定要做什么小蛋糕啊
so we can figure out what we're making.
这味道像臭脚似的
That tastes like a foot!
现在再加点面粉
And now I'm using some flour.
我们烘焙时都用面粉
We use flour when we bake.
对吧 麦克斯
Right, Max?
好辣
Oh, that is hot.
太辣了
Ooh, that's too hot.
跟满身火焰的恶魔屁股一样烫[辣]
That is hot as the devil's ass!
我的嘴要烧起来了 那臭脚味的玩意呢
Oh, my mouth is on fire. Where's that foot thing?
让开 我来帮你 这是什么
Move over, I'll help you. What is this?
是香草
It's vanilla.
是甜的 麦克斯 是甜的
It's sweet, Max! It's sweet.
再选个别的材料就行了
Now we just have to pick something else.
这个吧 火腿
There, ham.
我们可以做个香草火腿小蛋糕
We're making a vanilla ham cupcake.
就是这个了 香草火腿
That's it! Vanilla ham!
你就是个香草[白人]猪扒妹
You're a vanilla ham!
很好 继续羞辱我
Good, insult me!
你要恢复正常了 麦克斯 来吧
Yes, you're coming out of it, Max, here we go.
我们注定要失败
We're not going anywhere.
虽然上了我爱的节目 但我要输了
I'm on my show and I'm losing.
别想着我们在上节目
Forget we're on the show.
想象我们在餐厅里 奥列格大麻抽傻了
Pretend we're in the diner, and Oleg is stoned,
而我们手边有这些材料
and we have all these ingredients
厨房外是一群吵着要小蛋糕的顾客
and we just got slammed with people who all want cupcakes.
你当时怎么教我的
What do you tell me to do?
首先 我会叫你滚蛋
Well, first, I tell you to leave
我才好跟奥列格一起抽大麻
So I can get stoned with Oleg.
如果我抽傻了
Okay, if I was stoned,
我会怎么想灵魂食物
what would I know about soul food?
卢达克里斯[黑人说唱歌手]
Ludacris!
他总是在说
Is always talking about
他有多喜欢松饼加炸鸡早餐
how much he loves waffles with chicken.
炸鸡松饼小蛋糕
Chicken and waffle cupcake!
没错 炸鸡松饼小蛋糕
Yes! Chicken and waffles!
你们注意点了 女士们
You better watch it, girls.
巨乳姐跟装模作样妞联手做的
Here comes chicken and waffles
炸鸡松饼小蛋糕要上场了
from big boobs and try hard.
卢达克里斯如果在这
As Ludacris would say,
他会说 小妞让开 别挡爷的路[歌词]
move, bitch, get out the way.
上啊 我们要使出全力
Let's go, girl. We gotta bring it.
我们要发功 使出十成功力
We gotta shut this down. We are bringing our "A" game.
是时候将小蛋糕生意名扬天下了
It's time to put our cupcake business on the map.
我们一定行 天啊
We got this. Oh, my God.
我把烂句全了说一遍
I said them all.
清空搅拌器 我们还有时间
Empty the mixer. We still have time.
瞧这金发傻蛋
Look at the blonde dumb-dumb.
恭喜你啊 麦克斯
Congratulations, Max!
苏菲 我们没赢
Sophie, we didn't get it.
恭喜你啊 卡洛琳
Oh, congratulations, Caroline!
苏菲 我说了 我们没被选上
Sophie, I told you, we didn't get picked.
那你要我怎么办
What am I supposed to do,
揣着整包的碎纸花 啥事不干吗
walk around with a purse full of confetti?
我很遗憾 姑娘们
I'm so sorry, ladies.
但常言道
But you know what they say,
"当上帝关上了门 你就来这工作"
when God closes a door, you work here.
就只是出师不利嘛
It just wasn't our day.
刚开始我们惊慌失措
We got flustered at first,
但我们最后还是做出了好蛋糕啊
but we did end up making a great cupcake.
就承认吧
Oh, say it.
我们被卡特里娜飓风袭击了
We got hit by hurricane Katrina.
的确 虽然不想相信
True. Hard to believe,
但另一对的品牌特色更加出色
but the other team had a better brand.
拜托哦
Oh, please.
把失败怪罪于多年之前的天灾
Blaming it on a disaster from years ago.
苏菲 当时你又不在 你哪能...
Well, Sophie, you weren't there, so I don't think you--
我不想听
Oh, I don't want to hear it!
本来你们有大好的接活机会
I mean, you had huge opportunity with duza day.
但你们不干这正经活
But you passed on the real job
选择不切实际的上电视找突破
waiting for your big break on the TV show,
你们美国人都这样
Just like everyone else in America.
想靠旁门左道 走捷径取得成功
So you tried to take a shortcut to success
下场就是满嘴的碎纸花
and you end up with a mouth full of confetti.
苏菲说得对
Sophie's right.
我们上电视就只是心里想着能
We went on television with the ridiculous expectation
不努力就轻松成功
that we'd make it overnight.
但这条路不适合我们
But that's not who we are.
我们只能靠苦干实干
We're gonna have to do it the hard way.
稳扎稳打
Slow and steady.
走慢乌龟与骚鸡鸡路线
The tortoise and the whore.
我能说啥呢 "糖裸淋"
Well, what can I say, "Caramel?"
对了 这是你的"艺名"
By the way, that's your whore name.
看来我们还是得用老方法
Looks like it's back to selling cakes
慢慢"叫卖"小蛋糕了
one car at a time.
我把"卢达克里斯小蛋糕"放展示盒里吧
I'll just put these "Ludacris specials" in the display case.
行啊 "肉贵姐"
You do that, "Cinnamon."
别乱取 我已经有"艺名"了
Oh, no, I actually have a whore name,
不是你取的那个
And that's not it.
那是啥
What is it?
"卖客湿"啊 废话
Max. Duh.